

M. Recki Naufal L.



Jln. tipar kp.tipar RT01/04 kel.ciawi kec.ciawi kab.bogor



rekinaufal@gmail.com



in M. Recki Naufal L.



082124712159

ABOUT ME

Current position as Staff IT Programmer at PT.Sanjaya International Fishery, I have experience as Software Developer more than 1 year, on 2 coporate like PT.Zamasco Mitra Solusindo, and for now at PT.Sanjaya International Fishery. aside from that I have freelance experience more than 1 project .

EDUCATION

2017-2021 UNIVERSITAS BINANIAGA INDONESIA (UNBIN) Sistem Informasi (SI)

2015-2017 SMK WIKRAMA BOGOR Rekayasa Perangkat Lunak

COMPETIENCE

- CodeIgniter
- Laravel
- PHP
- HTML
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- JavaScript
- Jquery
- RestAPI
- .NET
- MYSOL
- SQL Server
- Github
- Postman
- SQL Yog
- Ajax
- API

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

- BEM UNBIN divisi pengkajian dan keilmuan (2017 -2021)
- Panitia Bidang Mentor Ospek UNBIN 2019 -2020

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. Sanjaya International Fishery (Januari 2022 - Current)

1. ERP Project

Project Description: ERP project

Job Description:

- Create flow program
- Create database
- Create CMS

Technology / Tools:

- O HTML 5
- Javascript
- o CSS
- o Bootstrap
- o PHP Laravel 8
- Ajax
- o MYSQL
- 2. Company Profile and Catalog

Project Description: Website Company Profile and Catalog Job Description:

- Create flow program
- o Create database
- Create frontend
- Create Backend

Technology / Tools:

- o HTML 5
- Javascript
- o CSS
- Bootstrap
- o PHP Codeigniter 3
- o MYSQL

WORK EXPERIENCE

PT. ZAMASCO SOLUSINDO (September 2021 - Oktober 2021)
Project Description: Badan Nasional Penanggulangan Bencana (BNPB NODIN)

Job Description:

- Create database
- Create CMS

Technology / Tools:

- HTML 5
- Javascript
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PHP Laravel 8
- Ajax
- MYSQL

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

PT. Global Gemilang Sukses (November 2021 - Desember 2021) Project Description : Website company profile and catalog Job Description :

- Create flow program
- Create database
- Create frontend
- Create backend

Technology / Tools:

- HTML 5
- Javascript
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PHP CodeIgniter 3
- MYSQL

Wedding Invitation

Project Description: Website Wedding Invitation

Job Description:

- Create flow program
- Create database
- Create frontend
- Create backend

Technology / Tools:

- HTML 5
- Javascript
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PHP Laravel 9
- MYSQL
- API
- Ajax

FREELANCE EXPERIENCE

Jobfair Kemenaker Kota Bekasi (Agustus 2022 - September 2022)

Project Description: Website Jobfair

Job Description:

- Create flow program
- Create database
- Create frontend
- Create backend

Technology / Tools :

- HTML 5
- API
- Ajax
- Javascript
- CSS
- Bootstrap
- PHP Laravel 9
- MYSQL
- Javascript